Guide to the Public Art Fund Archive MSS.270
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XV: Printed Material, 1963-2008; 7 Linear Feet in 7 record cartons.
  - Kunstverein Hannover. Kenneth Snelson, 1971 (Box 136, Folder 4)
  - L'acceuil d'artistes en residence temporaire en France, 1992 (Box 136, Folder 5)
  - La Jolla Museum of Contemporary Art. Jene Highstein, 1987 (Box 136, Folder 6)
  - La Jolla Museum of Contemporary Art. Sitings, 1986 (Box 136, Folder 7)
  - LaSalle Partners. The Private Eye in Public Art, 1997 (Box 136, Folder 8)
  - Laumeier Sculpture Park. Laumeier Sculpture Park: First Decade 1976-1986 (Box 136, Folder 9)
  - Laumeier Sculpture Park. Jackie Ferrara and Mary Miss, 1987 (Box 136, Folder 10)
  - Leicester, Andrew. Sketchbook, 1988 (Box 136, Folder 11)
  - Lennon, Weinberg, Inc. Raoul Hague, 1990 (Box 136, Folder 12)
  - Lincoln Center. Painting and Sculpture at Lincoln Center, undated (Box 136, Folder 13)
  - Livability Digest, vol. 2 no. 1, 1982 (Box 136, Folder 14)
  - Long Island University. Judith Murray: Painting, Ursula von Rydingsvard: Sculpture, 1985 (Box 136, Folder 15)
  - Long Island University. Public Art Project, undated (Box 136, Folder 16)
  - Lotan, Yael. Tumarkin: Etchings, Texts, Photos & Drawings, 1980 (Box 136, Folder 17)
  - Louis K. Meisel Gallery. Oded Halahmy, 1981 (Box 136, Folder 18)
  - Louis K. Meisel Gallery. Oded Halahmy: Bronze Sculptures 1981-1986, 1987 (Box 136, Folder 19)
  - Mackenzie Art Gallery. Pat Steir: Self-Portrait, 1991 (Box 136, Folder 20)
  - Madison Art Center. Owen Morrel: Works 1976-1984 (Box 136, Folder 21)
  - Marisa del Re Gallery. Arman's Orchestra, 1983 (Box 136, Folder 22)
  - Marisa del Re Gallery. IIIeme Biennale de Sculpture Montecarlo 1991 (Box 136, Folder 23)
  - Marlborough Chelsea. Beverly Pepper: The Magma Series, 2001 (Box 136, Folder 24)
  - Marlborough Gallery. Abakanowicz: Recent Exhibitions and Installations, undated (Box 136, Folder 25)
  - Marlborough Gallery. Charles Ginnever: Large Scale Sculpture, 1983 (Box 136, Folder 26)
  - Marlborough Gallery. Fernando Botero: Drawings on Canvas, 1993 (Box 136, Folder 27)
  - Marlborough Gallery. Magdalena Abakanowicz: Arboreal Architecture, 1992 (Box 136, Folder 28)
  - Marlborough Gallery. Marisol, 1995 (Box 136, Folder 29)
  - Maurine Littleton Gallery. Joyce Scott and Susan Plum, 1999 (Box 136, Folder 30)
  - Max Hutchinson Gallery. Clement Meadmore, undated (Box 136, Folder 31)
  - Max Hutchinson Gallery. James Buchanan, 1983 (Box 136, Folder 32)
  - Max Protetch Gallery. Scott Burton: Chaise Longings, 1996 (Box 136, Folder 33)
  - Max Protetch Gallery. Scott Burton: The Concrete Work, 1992 (Box 136, Folder 34)
  - Max Protetch Gallery. Siah Armajani: Elements, 1991 (Box 136, Folder 35)
  - MB Modern. Emily Mason, 1999 (Box 136, Folder 36)
  - McElheny, Josiah. The Metal Party, 2002 (Box 136, Folder 37)
  - Menegon, Lieutenant Colonel David J.. History of the Knickerbocker Greys, 2002 (Box 136, Folder 38)
  - Merriewold West Gallery. Outdoor Sculpture 1974 (Box 136, Folder 39)
  - Messner, Ann. Bearing Witness, undated (Box 136, Folder 40)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art. New York City Public Sculpture by 19th-Century American Artists, 1974 (Box 136, Folder 41)
  - Michael Rosenfeld Gallery. Burgoyne Diller, 1998 (Box 136, Folder 42)
  - Midtown Payson Galleries. Joyce Kozloff, 1995 (Box 136, Folder 43)
  - Milgo Art Systems. Kosso Eloul, undated (Box 136, Folder 44)
  - Minnesota Highway Project, undated (Box 136, Folder 45)
  - Moffett, Donald. Blue [NY], 1997 (Box 136, Folder 46)
  - Municipal Art Society. Adopt-A-Monument, 1987 (Box 136, Folder 47)
  - Murdock, Robert M. The Sculpture of Bill Freeland, 1989 (Box 136, Folder 48)
  - Musee Departemental des Vosges. Michel Gerard, 1983 (Box 136, Folder 49)
  - Museum of Art, The Pennsylvania State University. Rodney Alan Greenblat's Reality and Imagination; Two Taste Treats in One, 1987 (Box 136, Folder 50)
  - The Museum of Contemporary Art, Los Angeles. Saber es poder/interventions, 1994 (Box 136, Folder 51)
  - The Museum of Modern Art, New York. Painting and Sculpture in the Museum of Modern Art, 1988 (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - Museum of Modern Art, Oxford. David Mach: Towards a Landscape, 1985 (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - Nassau County Museum of Fine Art. Allen Bertoldi 1941-1981: Retrospective, 1983 (Box 137, Folder 3)
  - Nassau County Museum of Fine Art. Edward Mayer: Sculpture, 1980 (Box 137, Folder 4)
  - Nassau County Museum of Fine Arts. Mary Miss: Perimeters/Pavilions/Decoys, 1978 (Box 137, Folder 5)
  - Nassau County Museum of Fine Arts. Passings: Robert Stackhouse, 1980 (Box 137, Folder 6)
  - Nassau County Museum of Fine Art. Richard Nonas, 1985 (Box 137, Folder 7)
  - National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration. Five Artists at NOAA, 1985 (Box 137, Folder 8)
  - New Jersey State Museum. A Force of Repetition, 1990 (Box 137, Folder 9)
  - Nohra Haime Gallery. Keith Milow: Recent Work, 1995 (Box 137, Folder 10)
  - Nohra Haime Gallery. Lika Mutal: Recent Sculpture, 1990 (Box 137, Folder 11)
  - Nohra Haime Gallery. Lika Mutal: Stone Sculpture, 1993 (Box 137, Folder 12)
  - Nohra Haime Gallery. Menashe Kadishman: Small Sculpture, 1990 (Box 137, Folder 13)
  - Nonas, Richard. Agricultural Doubt, 1987 (Box 137, Folder 14)
  - Nordman, Maria. De Musica, undated (Box 137, Folder 15)
  - NYSCA Visual Artists Program: Responses from the Organizational Profile Questionnaire, 1992 (Box 137, Folder 16)
  - The Oakland Museum. Public Sculpture/Urban Environment, 1974 (Box 137, Folder 17)
  - Orte: Kunst fur offentliche Raume, 1992 (Box 137, Folder 18)
  - Oscarsson Hood Gallery. Marsha Pels, 1984-1985 (Box 137, Folder 19)
  - The Pace Gallery. Ape & Cat, 1993 (Box 137, Folder 20)
  - The Pace Gallery. Barry Flanagan, 1990 (Box 137, Folder 21)
  - The Parks Council and Central Park Conservancy. Public Space for Public Life, 1993 (Box 137, Folder 22)
  - Patrick Dougherty, undated (Box 137, Folder 23)
  - Paula Cooper Gallery. Tony Smith: Stinger, 1999 (Box 137, Folder 24)
  - Percent for Art: A Review, 1991 (Box 137, Folder 25)
  - Philippe Staib Gallery. Owen Morrel, 1991 (Box 137, Folder 26)
  - Philippe Staib Gallery. Zero Higashida, 1991 (Box 137, Folder 27)
  - Pittsburgh Center for the Arts. Michael Hardesty, 1990 (Box 137, Folder 28)
  - Pittsburgh Center for the Arts. Robert Arneson: Points of View, 1986 (Box 137, Folder 29)
  - Platz-Haus Salgau. Kurt Laurenz Metzler, 1996 (Box 137, Folder 30)
  - Plenn, Virginia & Jaime. A Guide to Modern Mexican Murals, 1963 (Box 137, Folder 31)
  - The Port Authority of NY & NJ. The Arts as an Industry, 1983 (Box 137, Folder 32)
  - Pratt Institute Department of Exhibitions. Bridges, 1983 (Box 137, Folder 33)
  - Public Art Development Trust, undated (Box 137, Folder 34)
  - Public Art Fund. Allison Smith: The Muster, 2005 (Box 137, Folder 35)
  - Public Art Fund. Contemporary Art at the Embassy Suites Hotel in New York City, 2000 (Box 137, Folder 36)
  - Public Art Fund. Everyday Eden, 2007 (Box 137, Folder 37)
  - Public Art Fund. Field Guide to the Wildlife of Madison Square Park, 2002 (Box 137, Folder 38)
  - Public Art Fund. Francis Alys: The Modern Procession, 2004 (Box 137, Folder 39)
  - Public Art Fund. Governors Island, 2004 (Box 137, Folder 40)
  - Public Art Fund. The Invisible City, undated (Box 137, Folder 41)
  - Public Art Fund. Issues, 1989-1992 (Box 137, Folder 42)
  - Public Art Fund. Julian Opie, 2004 (Box 137, Folder 43)
  - Public Art Fund. Now Entering Brooklyn, 2003 (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - Public Art Fund Publications: 01, 02, 03, 04, 05, 06, 2000-2003 (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - Public Art Fund. Semiprecious, 2004 (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - Public Art Fund. Roxy Paine/Bluff, undated (Box 138, Folder 4)
  - Public Art Fund. Ten Years of Public Art 1972-1982 (Box 138, Folder 5)
  - Public Art Fund. Tony Oursler: The Influence Machine, undated (Box 138, Folder 6)
  - Public Art Fund. Trapdoor, 2008 (Box 138, Folder 7)
  - Public Art Fund. Urban Paradise: Gardens in the City, 1994 (Box 138, Folder 8)
  - Public Art Fund. The World is Round, 2006 (Box 138, Folder 9)
  - Public Art Works: 1989 Annual Catalog (Box 138, Folder 10)
  - Public Arts Council of the Municipal Art Society. Pierre Clerk at Waterside, 1977 (Box 138, Folder 11)
  - Produzentengalerie Hamburg. Bogomir Ecker, 1987 (Box 138, Folder 12)
  - P.S.1. Contemporary Art Center. Clockwork 2000, 1999 (Box 138, Folder 13)
  - Queens College, City University of New York. The Ways of Wood, 1984-1985 (Box 138, Folder 14)
  - The Queens Museum. Sculpture of the Eighties, 1987 (Box 138, Folder 15)
  - Randolph Street Gallery. Outdoor Installations 1979-1980 (Box 138, Folder 16)
  - Reed, Henry Hope, Robert M. McGee, and Esther Mipaas. Bridges of Central Park, 1990 (Box 138, Folder 17)
  - Rist, Pipilotti. I'm not the girl who misses much, 1994 (Box 138, Folder 18)
  - Robert Elkon Gallery. William Tucker: Sculpture and Drawings, 1982 (Box 138, Folder 19)
  - Robert Miller Gallery. Juan Hamilton, 1987 (Box 138, Folder 20)
  - Ronald Feldman Fine Arts, Inc., and the Village Voice. The 1984 Show (Box 138, Folder 21)
  - Royal Festival Hall. Silvio Wolf: The Elsewhere [A/V: CD-Rom catalogue], 1999 (Box 138, Folder 22)
  - Ruth Siegel Gallery. Creighton Michael: Constructions 1990 (Box 138, Folder 23)
  - Sacramento Metropolitan Arts Commission. Sculpture Sacramento, 1982 (Box 138, Folder 24)
  - Salvatore Ala Gallery. Antony Gormley, 1984 (Box 138, Folder 25)
  - Salvatore Ala Gallery. David Finn: Masked Figures, 1986 (Box 138, Folder 26)
  - San Francisco Department of City Planning. The Downtown Plan, 1983 (Box 138, Folder 27)
  - San Francisco Museum of Art. Beverly Pepper: Sculpture 1971-1975 (Box 138, Folder 28)
  - San Francisco Museum of Modern Art. The Clos Pegase Design Competition, 1985 (Box 138, Folder 29)
  - San Jose Museum of Art. Fletcher Benton, 1982 (Box 138, Folder 30)
  - Sculpture 3: New York Artists on Tour, 1973 (Box 138, Folder 31)
  - Sculpture Off the Pedestal, 1973 (Box 138, Folder 32)
  - Sculpture Outside in Cleveland, 1981 (Box 138, Folder 33)
  - Sculpture Outdoors. Out of the Woods, 1990 (Box 138, Folder 34)
  - SculptureCenter. Alan Finkel: SculptureCenter Prize 2001 (Box 138, Folder 35)
  - Seattle Arts Commission. Artwork Network, 1984 (Box 138, Folder 36)
  - Shingu, Susumu. Windcircus, 1989 (Box 138, Folder 37)
  - Sidney Janis Gallery. R.M. Fischer: New Sculpture, 1991 (Box 138, Folder 38)
  - Socrates Sculpture Park. Artists Choose Artists, 1988 (Box 138, Folder 39)
  - Socrates Sculpture Park. Sculptors Working, 1989 (Box 138, Folder 40)
  - Socrates Sculpture Park. Socrates Sculpture Park Inaugural Exhibition, 1986 (Box 138, Folder 41)
  - Soffer, Sasson. Sasson Soffer: In the City of New York, 1985 (Box 138, Folder 42)
  - Soffer, Sasson. Sasson Soffer: Metal Sculptures, 1985 (Box 138, Folder 43)
  - Spitzer, Serge. Hannover Relevator, 1990 (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - Stadtische Kunsthalle Dusseldorf. Bogomir Ecker, 1989 (Box 139, Folder 2)
  - Stadtische Kunsthalle Mannheim. Michel Gerard: Skulpturen 1976-1988 (Box 139, Folder 3)
  - Stadtisches Kunstmuseum Bonn. Bogomir Ecker, 1987 (Box 139, Folder 4)
  - Stark Gallery. Jill Baroff, 1995 (Box 139, Folder 5)
  - Statens Konstrad. Byggnadsintegrerad Konst Pa Kemiska Ovningslaboratoriet, Stockholms Universitet, Frescati, 1996 (Box 139, Folder 6)
  - Statens Konstrad. Columna, 1996 (Box 139, Folder 7)
  - Statens Konstrad. Gestaltning, av broplan, molndal, 2000 (Box 139, Folder 8)
  - Statens Konstrad. Maaria Wirkkala: Forskarcellerna, 2001 (Box 139, Folder 9)
  - Statens Konstrad. Partner sokes., undated (Box 139, Folder 10)
  - Storm King Art Center. Mia Westerlund Roosen: Sculpture and Drawings, 1994 (Box 139, Folder 11)
  - The Tel Aviv Museum. Myth Transformed: Painting and Monumental Sculpture of Menashe Kadishman, 1987 (Box 139, Folder 12)
  - Third Eye Centre. Thomas Lawson, 1990 (Box 139, Folder 13)
  - TSWA 3D, undated (Box 139, Folder 14)
  - Tyler Galleries. Jerry Kearns: Deep Cover: The Deadly Art of Illusion, 1991 (Box 139, Folder 15)
  - University of California, Irvine, Fine Arts Gallery. James Ford: A Survey, 1980-1983 (Box 139, Folder 16)
  - University Gallery, University of Massachusetts at Amherst. Jeffrey Brosk, 1987 (Box 139, Folder 17)
  - U.S. Department of Transportation. Aesthetics in Transportation, 1980 (Box 139, Folder 18)
  - Vancouver Association for Noncommercial Culture. Adverse Practises, undated (Box 139, Folder 19)
  - Vancouver Association for Noncommercial Culture. Urban Subjects, 1988 (Box 139, Folder 20)
  - Van der Marck, Jan. Arman, 1984 (Box 139, Folder 21)
  - Vassar College Art Gallery. Patsy Norvell, 1979 (Box 139, Folder 22)
  - The Venice Biennale '90/The Israeli Pavilion. Dorchin, 1990 (Box 139, Folder 23)
  - Vermont International Sculpture Symposium, 1973 (Box 139, Folder 24)
  - Victoria Munroe Gallery. Christopher Hewat: Sculpture, 1990 (Box 139, Folder 25)
  - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts/Richmond. Installations, 1986 (Box 139, Folder 26)
  - Visual Arts Program, National Endowment for the Arts. Insights/On Sites, 1984 (Box 139, Folder 27)
  - Walter/Mcbean Gallery, San Francisco Art Institute. Joyce J. Scott: Images Concealed, 1995 (Box 139, Folder 28)
  - Wave Hill Sculpture Garden. Figure in the Landscape, 1978 (Box 139, Folder 29)
  - Weatherspoon Art Gallery. Ronald Bladen: Drawings and Sculptural Models, 1995 (Box 139, Folder 30)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art. Another Chance for Cities, 1970 (Box 139, Folder 31)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art. Contemporary American Sculpture: 1970 Annual Exhibition (Box 139, Folder 32)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art. Developments in Recent Sculpture, 1981 (Box 139, Folder 33)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art at Equitable Center. Video Art: Expanded Forms, 1988 (Box 139, Folder 34)
  - Wildenstein. Rhonda Roland Shearer: Ambiguous Figures, New Bronze Works, 1990 (Box 139, Folder 35)
  - Yorkshire Sculpture Park/The Nelson-Atkins Museum of Art/The Indianapolis Museum of Art. Ursula von Rydingsvard, 1997 (Box 139, Folder 36)
  - Zabriskie Gallery. Stuart Davis: Murals, 1976 (Box 139, Folder 37)
- Series XVI: Archived Website, October 2025-ongoing; 1 websites in 1 archived website.
  Accruals
  New site crawls are accrued semiannually.
  Due to technical or privacy issues, archived websites may not be exact copies of the original website at the time of the web crawl. Certain file types will not be captured dependent on how they are embedded in the site. Other parts of websites that the crawler has difficulty capturing includes Javascript, streaming content, database-driven content, and highly interactive content. Full-Text searches of archived websites are available at https://archive-it.org/organizations/567.
  Appraisal
  Crawl was limited to domains and subdomains of publicartfund.org in order to remain within the collection scope and data constraints.
  The archived website for the Public Art Fund contains images and descriptions of current and past public art exhibitions dating back to 1973. The website also includes public program event descriptions dating back to 1999 and videos with curators and artists.
- Oversize Series I: City Walls
  This series contains original mock-ups of mural designs created on canvas by multiple artists during the City Walls program.
  - City Walls Canvas - Milicevic, Tania (Mercer & 3rd) - 1970 - 1 of 2, cuid5975; 1 item one painting; 100.5 x 43 inches. (Box 113)
    Artist: Tania Milicevic
    Paintings (visual works)
  - City Walls Canvas - Milicevic, Tania (Mercer & 3rd) - 1970 - 2 of 2, 100.5 x 43 inches. (Roll-storage R1)
  - City Walls Canvas - Pekarsky, Mel- (Bleecker and Lafayette) 1970, 96 x 49 inches. (Roll-storage R1)
  - City Walls Canvas - Williams, Todd - (Livingston & Bond) - 1970, 49 x 58 inches. (Roll-storage R1)
  - City Walls - New York Times Poster (Newsprint), 1970 (Box 116, Folder 1)
- Oversize Series II: Public Arts Council
  This series contains posters and site plans pertaining to projects of the Public Arts Council.
  - New York Professional Women Artists: Walk Through Art (Exhibition Poster), 1974 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Tumarkin, Igael - PAC [Public Arts Council] Project Site Plans, 1976 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Valinski, Dennis - "At Waterside" - Poster, 1976 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - "Yield Brother" Posters, 1971-1972 (Folder 12)
- Oversize Series VI: Project Files
  This series contains oversize material pertaining to projects of the Public Art Fund, including site plans, original drawings, signs, and posters. Notable objects include sixteen original signs from Martin Wong's "Traffic Signs for the Hearing Impaired", completed in 1990, and an original poster for Agnes Denes "Wheatfield" (1982).
  - Torffield, Marvin - "Volume" Poster, 1980 (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Wendkos, Gina, 1980 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Wells, David - Central Park Site Plan, 1981 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Finkel, Alan - "View for the Catenary Curve Empire" - Fulton Ferry State Park - Site Plan, 1981 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Denes, Agnes - "Wheatfield" Poster, 1982 (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - The Bridges Show - poster, 1983 (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - Aprile, Tom - "Family Room With a View" - site plan, 1984 (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - Rothfarb, Ed - Proposal - Walt Whitman Park - site plans, 1984 (Box 116, Folder 12)
  - Chin, Mel - site plan, 1984 (Box 116, Folder 13)
  - Aycock, Alice - Doris Freedman Plaza site plans, 1986 (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - Elrod, Biff - Site Plan - 1 of 2, 1986 (Box 116, Folder 15)
  - Elrod, Biff - Site Plan - 2 of 2, 1986 (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - Red Spot Outdoor Slide Theater, [1986] (Box 116, Folder 17)
  - Artschwager, Richard - 2 site plans, 1987 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - "Newsstand 88" - poster for submissions, 1988 (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Schafer, David - poster, 1988 (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Dwyer, Nancy - "Get you there for sure" - Transit posters, 1989; 36 x 10 inches. (Roll-storage R7)
  - Dwyer, Nancy - "Transit Gets You There" (subway ad), 1989 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Gaskins, Franco "The Great", 1989 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Gianakos, Steve - Bronx Zoo - Transit Posters, 1989; 45 x 30 inches. (Flat-file-folder 5)
  - Gianakos, Steve - Bronx Zoo - Transit Poster, 1989 (Folder 12)
  - Fulbrecht, William - "Bill of Rights" - Site Plans, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Video Drive-in poster, 1990 (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - Wong, Martin - "Traffic Signs for the Hearing Impaired" - Stop, 1990; cuid6048; 5 items five signs; 29.5 x 30 inches. (Box 127, Item MSS.270.cuid6048)
    Direction signs.; Works of art.
  - Wong, Martin - "Traffic Signs for the Hearing Impaired" - School for the Deaf, 1990; cuid6049; 4 items four signs; 29.5 x 30 inches. (Item MSS.270.cuid6049)
  - Wong, Martin - "Traffic Signs for the Hearing Impaired" - One Way, 1990; cuid6050; 4 items four signs; 35.5 x 12 inches. (Box 126, Item MSS.270.cuid6050)
  - Wong, Martin - "Traffic Signs for the Hearing Impaired" - Yellow People Crossing, 1990; cuid6051; 3 items three signs; 29.5 x 30 inches. (Box 144, Item MSS.270.cuid6051)
  - Gran Fury, "Spanish" - "Simplemente Muren" "Women Don't get AIDS they just die from it"- Bus Shelter Poster, 1991; 48 x 71 inches. (Roll-storage Shared Fales 047)
  - Guerrilla Girls - "First they take away a woman's right to choose, now they're censoring art", 1991; cuid6040; 1 item one mural composed of 10 posters (Box 129)
    Posters.
  - Kruger "Help" - Bus shelter poster, 1991; 48 x 69 inches. (Roll-storage Shared Fales 047)
  - Ressler, Robert - "Mantis" - Site plan, 1991 (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Ressler, Robert - Columbus Park: "Mantis" - Proposal, 1991 (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Rockburne, Dorthea - "Vary form, Curve" + "Ship Curves", 1991 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Allen, Jules - Bus Shelter poster - 1 of 4, 1992; 48 x 68 inches. (Roll-storage Shared Fales 047)
  - Allen, Jules - Bus Shelter poster - 2 of 4, 1992; 48 x 68 inches. (Roll-storage Shared Fales 047)
  - Allen, Jules - Bus Shelter poster - 3 of 4, 1992; 48 x 68 inches. (Roll-storage Shared Fales 047)
  - Allen, Jules - Bus Shelter poster - 4 of 4, 1992; 48 x 68 inches. (Roll-storage Shared Fales 047)
  - Deon, Richard - "Hike New York/Long Island City" - Hand-painted sign, 1992 (Box 117, Folder 8)
    Description: Richard Long - "Hike New York" hand-painted sign Media: Paper mounted in plastic with tape Dimensions: 23.5 x 16.5 inches
  - Deon, Richard - Hike New York - Long Island City, 1992; cuid6052; 1 item one sign (Box 144, Item MSS.270.cuid6052)
  - Deon, Richard - Hike New York - Long Island City -- Museum of the Moving Image .3 mi, 1992; cuid6053; 1 item one sign (Box 126, Item MSS.270.cuid6053)
  - Deon, Richard - Hike New York - Long Island City -- Sunnyside Historic District .5 mi, Thompson Hill Park .8 mi, Thalia Spanish Theatre .8 mi, 1992; cuid6054 (Box 126, Item MSS.270.cuid6054)
  - Trans-Voices/Blain, Dominique - "US Nickel, Discontinued in 1938", 1992; 60 x 46 inches. (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Trans-Voices/Boltanski, Christian - "Avis de Recherche/Notice", 1992; 60 x 46 inches. (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Trans-Voices/Cazal, Philippe - "Empire" English, 1992; 60 x 46 inches. (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Trans-Voices/Ennadre, Touhami - "Mains du Monde", 1992; 60 x 46 inches. (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Trans-Voices/Gerz, Jochen -"Comment Vivre/How to Live", 1992; 60 x 46 inches. (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Trans-Voices/Jaar, Alfredo - "1992", 60 x 46 inches. (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - Trans-Voices/Lafontaine, Marie-Jo - "Nous sommes tous des ombres/We are all shadows" [English], 1992; 60 x 46 inches. (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - Trans-Voices/Lafontaine, Marie-Jo - "Nous sommes tous des ombres/We are all shadows" [French] (Rolled), 1992; 60 x 46 inches. (Roll-storage R7)
  - Trans-Voices/Messager, Annette - "Prude America, France Impertinente", 1992; 60 x 46 inches. (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - Trans-Voices/Simmons, Laurie - "Lying Objects", 1992; 60 x 46 inches. (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Trans-Voices/Simpson, Lorna - "Untitled", 1992; 60 x 46 inches. (Box 118, Folder 10)
  - Trans-Voices/Teraoka, Masami - "AIDS World Story", 1992; 60 x 46 inches. (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - Trans-Voices/Gerz, Jochen [French] (Rolled), 1992; 60 x 46 inches. (Roll-storage R7)
  - Botero, Fernando - Poster, 1993; 30 x 45 inches. (Flat-file-folder 5)
  - Otterness, Tom - Site Plans, 1995 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Otterness, Tom - Transit Ad (Rolled), 1995; 11 x 70 inches. (Roll-storage R8)
  - Gonzalez, Maria Elena: Magic Carpet, 1999 (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - LeWitt, Sol - Embassy Suites Wall - site plan, 2000 (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - Long, Richard - Transit poster (Rolled) - 1 of 2, 2000 (Roll-storage R8)
  - Long, Richard - Transit poster (Rolled) - 2 of 2, 2000 (Roll-storage R8)
  - Otterness, Tom - Hilton Hotel - site plans (4 copies), 2000 (Box 117, Folder 11)
  - Westphalen, Olav - "E.S.U.S. Extremely Site Unspecific Sculpture" - Brochure, 2000 (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Goldsworthy, Andy: Museum of Jewish Heritage, 2003 (Box 117, Folder 12)
  - Williams, Clara - "The Price" -site plan, 2003 (Box 117, Folder 13)
  - Kentridge, William - "9 Drawings for Projection" - Posters, 2004 (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - West, Franz: "Recent Sculptures" - 2 Posters, 2004; 20 x 35 inches. (Box 117, Folder 14)
  - Aoshima, Chiho - "City Glow" - 2005/ "Little Boy" - 2 posters (Box 117, Folder 16)
  - Kawashima, Hideaki -"Fire" - 2004/ "Little Boy" - 2 posters, 2005 (Box 117, Folder 15)
  - Rubins, Nancy - "Placement of Truss", 2005 (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Takano, Aya - "A Night Walk - The Pink Walk Emerges" - 2005/ "Little Boy" - 2 posters (Box 117, Folder 16)
  - Tsubaki, Noboru - "Aesthetic Pollution" - 1991/ "Little Boy" - 2 posters, 2005 (Box 117, Folder 15)
  - Yamada, James - Proposals for "In the Public Realm", 2005 (Box 114, Folder 10)